javelin-tech.com 2014-06-21

# Privacy Policy - Privacy Practices for Javelin Website & Electronic Communications

## Privacy Practices for Javelin Website & Electronic Communications 

Welcome to this website, a service of Javelin Technologies Inc. This statement discloses the privacy practices for this website, including an explanation of which personally identifiable information of yours is collected; the organization collecting the information; how the information is used; with whom the information may be shared; which choices are available to you regarding collection, use and distribution of the information; the kind of security procedures that are in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information; and how you can correct any inaccuracies in the information. 

Questions regarding this statement should be directed to Javelin through one of the feedback forms you will find on the website, or by sending a notice by mail to Javelin Inc., 3457 Superior Court, Unit #1, Oakville, Ontario, Canada, L6L 0C4.

### **Information Collection and Use**

The information made available to Javelin falls into two categories: (1) information voluntarily supplied by visitors to the website and (2) tracking information recorded as visitors navigate through the website.

To make use of some features on our website visitors may need to register and provide certain information as part of the registration or request process. We may ask, for example, for your name, title, company, address, contact numbers, email address, and postal code. The information you supply will help us to offer you more personalized features, to tailor our website to your interests and make it more useful to you.

The more you tell us about yourself, the more value we can offer you. Supplying such information is entirely voluntary. But if you choose not to supply the information, we may be unable to provide you with the products and services we make available to other visitors to our website. And you will not be able to order selected products or services over our website unless you provide certain personally identifying information about yourself. When you submit any personally identifying information over this website, Javelin (a) will use the information for the purposes described at the time you submit it (for example, your name, company, address, telephone number, and email address provided while requesting one of our products or services will be used in connection with the processing and fulfillment of your order) and (b) may use the information to contact you to make you aware of other products and services of interest. Of course, if you want to remain completely anonymous, you're still free to take advantage of the publicly available content on our website without registration. 

To help make our site more responsive to the needs of our visitors, we invoke a standard feature of browser software, called a "cookie," to assign each visitor a unique, randomly generated number that temporarily resides on your computer. The cookie itself doesn't actually identify the visitor, just the particular computer session that a visitor uses to access our website. Unless you voluntarily identify yourself, we won't know who you are, even if we generate a cookie for your particular website session. The only personal information a cookie can contain is information you supply. 

We use cookies to help us tailor our website to your needs, to deliver a better, more personalized service, and to remember certain choices you've made so you don't have to re-enter them. We may use cookies to track the pages on our website visited by our users, for example. We can build a better website if we know which pages our users are visiting and how often. Of course, you can set your browser not to accept cookies, but if you do, you may not be able to take advantage of the personalized features enjoyed by other visitors to our website. 

In connection with the standard operation of Javelin's website, certain non-personally identifiable information about visitors to this website is recorded. This information is used primarily to tailor and enhance visitors' experience using the website. We may use this information in an aggregate, non-personally identifiable form to, among other things, measure the use of our website and determine which products and services are the most popular with website visitors. 

### **Sales E-mail Opt-out / Decline Consent**

Although most customers appreciate receiving notices from us, we understand the importance of providing you with choices. You may opt-out at any time after receiving a sales related email from Javelin. All sales related emails include an unsubscribe link so that you can decline further communication. Go to our [Email Preferences](http://solution.javelin-tech.com/connect) page to update how you receive communications from us.

### **Other Websites**

To make our website more valuable to our visitors, we may offer some features in conjunction with other providers. Our website may also include links to other websites whose privacy policies we don't control. Once you leave our website (you can tell where you are by checking the address -- known as a URL -- in the location bar on your browser), use of any information you provide is governed by the privacy policy of the operator of the website you're visiting. That policy may differ from ours. If you can't find the privacy policy of any of these websites via a link from the site's homepage, you should contact the website directly for more information.
